Sofía Fernández Moreno

Junior DevOps Engineer Madrid





Experience

Administrative and web designer

STA Villacarrillo S.L.

June 2017 - September 2017

Performing office tasks, such as managing the CRM of the company, adapting data in SEO. In addition to the maintenance of the company's website.

Internship trainee

Euroinnova Business School S.L.

November 2018 - May 2019

Work in computer and web development department, carrying out support tasks in the computer department in the company such as programming, requirements analysis, data storage, etc.

E-learning Content Designer

Innoforma E-Learning Technologies S.L.

May 2019 - September 2019

Expert in creation of formative content of the branch of Computing and **New Technologies**

Junior DevOps Engineer

Social Network Loycus S.A.

September 2019 - June 2020

Management, monitoring, alert and administration of the tools used within the life cycle of the applications and the platform. The tools used are Prometheus Stack, Kubernetes and Docker, GCP, Jenkins and Terraform.

DevOps Engineer

ALTEN (Airbus customer)

June 2020 - September 2020

Management, monitoring, alert and administration k8s infraestructure in Airbus Client.

Junior DevOps Engineer

IBM Global Technology Services

September 2020 - now

Management, monitoring, logging, alert and administration of the tools used within the life cycle of the applications and the platform, the tools used are all Prometheus Stack and Elastic Stack. Also provisioning all the infraestructure from DevOps Department with Ansible and managing the same with K8s and Openshift.



Education

MASTER SECURITY INFORMATION

November 2019 - July 2020

Universidad Europea de Madrid

BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

September 2015 - September 2019

Universidad de Granada

<>> Projects

Análisis v monitorización de **Security System**

DDoS Attacks

About me

Hi, my name is Sofía Fernández Moreno. I'm just about the most boring type of person you could possibly imagine. I like collecting logs with SIEM monitoring and living in the new era of the Cloud. I am not a robot. Please hire

Also proficient in developing CI/CD pipelines, Configuration Management Tools and deployments over large infrastructure.

Skills

Bash, Python, C++, Ruby, Groovy

Docker, Docker-Compose, DockerSwarm, Kubernetes and Openshift

CI/CD: Jenkins, Github Actions

Pentesting, Social Enginering, Nmap, Wireshark, Kali Linux Tools, Penetration testing OSINT Tools

Experience configuring NGINX, Apache, Redis, SSL and TLS certificates, PostgresSQL

LDAP and Active Directory

Cloud: GCP, Azure, AWS

Logging and Monitoring (ELK and Prometheus)

Contact

■ Madrid

chui274@gmail.com

655760279

sofiafernandezmoreno.github.io

in sofiafernandezmoreno

sofiafernandezmoreno